The Thomas and Ryan Families
Marist Archives and Special Collections
The Thomas and Ryan Families
2.1.3.3.1
Marist College
  Box 1517
- 2.1.3.3.1
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Ryan family, circa mid 1800s - 1887; 8 (Box 1517)
    - Mr. A. C. McCorkel [McCorkle]; father of Eunice Ryan and grandfather of Mrs. Lowell Thomas [Frances Ryan Thomas], 1
    - Verso: Mr. A. C. McCorkel [McCorkle]; father of Eunice Ryan and grandfather of Mrs. Lowell Thomas [Frances Ryan Thomas], 1-verso
    - Mrs. A. C. McCorkel [Nancy Emeline McCorkle]; mother of Eunice Ryan and grandmother of Mrs. Lowell Thomas [Frances Ryan Thomas], 2
    - Verso: Mrs. A. C. McCorkel [Nancy Emeline McCorkle]; mother of Eunice Ryan and grandmother of Mrs. Lowell Thomas [Frances Ryan Thomas], 2-verso
    - The picture of Eunice McCorkel [McCorkle] now Mrs. H. P. Ryan, the mother-in-law of Lowell Thomas, the commentator and world traveler - 1887, 3
    - Verso: The picture of Eunice McCorkel [McCorkle] now Mrs. H. P. Ryan, the mother-in-law of Lowell Thomas, the commentator and world traveler - 1887, 3-verso
    - Love and kisses to my Aunt Francie from Janet. I didn't attempt to send this in the big folder for fear you would never get it, 4
    - Verso: Love and kisses to my Aunt Francie from Janet. I didn't attempt to send this in the big folder for fear you would never get it, 4-verso
    - [Portrait of Young girl from Ryan family], 5
  - Norman Ryan [brother of Frances Ryan Thomas], 1918 -1940s; 9 (Box 1517)
    - Norman and Dott [Dorothy, wife of Norman Ryan], 1
    - Verso: Norman and Dott [Dorothy, wife of Norman Ryan], 1-verso
    - Norman Ryan, 2
    - Verso: Norman Ryan, 2-verso
    - Norman A. Ryan, 3
    - Verso:Norman A. Ryan, 3-verso
    - [Norman Ryan] Aug 1918, 4
    - Verso: Aug 1918, 4-verso
    - [Norman Ryan], 5
    - [Norman Ryan], 6
    - [Norman Ryan], 7
    - [Norman Ryan], 8
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Jackson family, 1928 - 1974; 10 (Box 1517)
    - 1925 Edith Jackson, 1
    - Verso: 1925 Edith Jackson, 1-verso
    - Caption: Wishing you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year! Verso: 1928, Rollo E. [Jackson] and Laura May Jackson, 2
    - Verso: 1928, Rollo E. [Jackson] and Laura May Jackson, 2-verso
    - 1931 R. E. Jackson and Donna, 3
    - Verso: 1931 R. E. Jackson and Donna, 3-verso
    - 1935, R. E. Jackson and Donna, 4
    - Verso: 1935, R. E. Jackson and Donna, 4-verso
    - R. E. and Laura [Jackson]; Donna and a second cousin, Beverly, 1936, 5
    - Verso: R. E. and Laura [Jackson]; Donna and a second cousin, Beverly, 1936, 5-verso
    - 1970 three remaining daughters at that time Lulu, Una, Edith; Cooks, Wash., 6
    - Verso: 1970 three remaining daughters at that time Lulu, Una, Edith; Cooks, Wash., 6-verso
    - Donna and Harold Schmitt - granddaughter of R.E. Jackson, daughter of Edith; 1974, 7
    - Verso: Donna and Harold Schmitt - granddaughter of R.E. Jackson, daughter of Edith; 1974, 7-verso
    - Front of Jackson home at Cooks, Washington; Edith and Bill Brandt (daughter of Rollo E. Jackson), 8
    - Verso: Front of Jackson home at Cooks, Washington; Edith and Bill Brandt (daughter of Rollo E. Jackson), 8-verso
    - Jackson property at Cooks on Columbia R. [River]. House to the right is the family home. Facing it to the left is the Brandt home, 9
    - Verso: Jackson property at Cooks on Columbia R. [River]. House to the right is the family home. Facing it to the left is the Brandt home, 9-verso
    - Rollo E. Jackson - February 5, 1940, 10
    - [Rollo E. Jackson and Laura Jackson (?)], 11
    - [Rollo E. Jackson], 12
    - [Rollo E. Jackson], 13
    - Note: Parentheses - married children and husband or wife Laurene, (Lyman, Una), (Rollo, June,) (Harry, Maxine, Effie,) RE Jackson, Laura, Lyman's father, Lulu, Don, Soren,) Delma, Oran, Edith, Earl, 14
    - [Rollo E. Jackson (?) and Laura Jackson (?), family and friends seated at dining table.], 15
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family ancestors, circa mid - late 1800s; 11 (Box 1517)
    - David and Pherbia Thomas. LT's gr'ndparents [grandparents], 1
    - Verso: David and Pherbia Thomas. LT's gr'ndparents [grandparents], 1-verso
    - Grandfather David Thomas and our grandmother. He was the survivor of the Civil War and the notorious Andersonville Prison. Later he became an unusually successful school teacher. Grandmother was a poetess...., 2
    - Note: Grandfather David Thomas and our grandmother. He was the survivor of the Civil War and the notorious Andersonville Prison. Later he became an unusually successful school teacher. Grandmother was a poetess...., 3
    - Uncle Dave Thomas; Aunt Phoebe Thomas [photograph is a duplicate of items 1-3 and appears to have been mislabeled], 4
    - Verso: Uncle Dave Thomas; Aunt Phoebe Thomas [photograph is a duplicate of items 1-3 and appears to have been mislabeled], 4-verso
    - L.T.'s grandfather David Thomas (seated) and his sisters Nancy, Sarah Jane, Phoebe. And his brothers - Absolom, Cyrus and Samuel Sackett, 5
    - Note: L.T.'s grandfather David Thomas (seated) and his sisters Nancy, Sarah Jane, Phoebe. And his brothers - Absolom, Cyrus and Samuel Sackett, 6
    - Grand Pa Thomas; Grandma Betty [possibly the great-grandparents of Lowell Thomas], 7
    - Verso: Grand Pa Thomas; Grandma Betty, 7-verso
    - Uncle Absie [Absolom]; Uncle Cyrus; Uncle Samuel; Aunt Nancy; Uncle Dave; Aunt Sallie; Aunt Auer[?]; Encampment at Columbus, Ohio about 1882, 8
    - Verso: Uncle Absie [Absolom]; Uncle Cyrus; Uncle Samuel; Aunt Nancy; Uncle Dave; Aunt Sallie; Aunt Auer[?]; Encampment at Columbus, Ohio about 1882, 8-verso
    - Uncle Absolem Thomas - Iowa, 9
    - Verso: Uncle Absolem Thomas - Iowa, 9-verso
    - Uncle Sam Slates and Aunt Sally - Iowa, 10
    - Verso: Uncle Sam Slates and Aunt Sally - Iowa, 10-verso
    - Caption: Samuel Slates; Verso: Iowa, 11
    - Verso: Iowa, 11-verso
    - LT Sr's [?] Great Uncle Fred Wagner, 12
    - Verso: LT Sr's [?] Great Uncle Fred Wagner, 12-verso
    - [David and Pherbia Thomas], 13
    - [Uncle Absie [Absolom]; Uncle Cyrus; Uncle Samuel; Aunt Nancy; Uncle Dave; Aunt Sallie; Aunt Auer[?]; Encampment at Columbus, Ohio about 1882], 14
    - [LT Sr's [?] Great Uncle Fred Wagner ], 15
    - [Uncle Samuel (?)], 16
    - [Uncle Samuel], 17
    - [Uncle Samuel], 18
    - [Uncle Samuel and Aunt Sallie (?)], 19
    - [Aunt Sallie (?)], 20
    - [Man and woman standing together for a photo], 21
    - [Fireplace], 22
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family, circa late 1800s - 1900s; 12 (Box 1517)
    - Helen Wagner Thomas, aged 10 mo., Weight 17 lbs, Oct 26, 1902; For Leuella, 1
    - Verso: Helen Wagner Thomas, aged 10 mo., Weight 17 lbs, Oct 26, 1902; For Leuella, 1-verso
    - Mercy Sackett Thomas, 2
    - Verso: Mercy Sackett Thomas, 2-verso
    - Charles Weaver Thomas, 3
    - Verso: Charles Weaver Thomas, 3-verso
    - Caption: Fraternally yours, Christian Segard, 4
    - [A young boy from the Thomas family], 5
    - [Portrait of a girl from the Thomas family], 6
    - [Portrait of a young lady from the Thomas family], 7
    - [Portrait of a young lady and a baby from the Thomas family], 8
    - [Portrait of a young boy from the Thomas family], 9
    - [Portrait of a young boy from the Thomas family], 10
    - [Portrait of a young boy from the Thomas family], 11
    - [Portrait of a young girl from the Thomas family], 12
    - Caption: Beem 1911, 13
    - [Man with hat, standing inside by the bar], 14
    - [Group of men smoking ciagarettes standing inside a small room], 15
    - [Caption: Leo (?) Ruschenberg's Cabin. Cripple Creek 1931. Fred Stone, Bert Ragon, (illegible), Leo Welch], 16
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family, circa 1930s - 1940s; 13 (Box 1517)
    - Who is this sweet little man?, 1
    - Verso: Who is this sweet little man? Mrs. Lowell Thomas, Palling, NY, 1-verso
    - [From the Thomas family, two little boys], 2
    - [Portrait of a woman from the Thomas family], 3
    - Caption: Mead Russell, 1931 [Portrait of a young girl, woman, and a boy (Lowell Thomas?)], 4
    - [Portrait of a man from the Thomas family], 5
  Box 1518
- 2.1.3.3.1
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family, circa 1930s - 1940s; 1 (Box 1518)
    - [Portrait of a woman from the Thomas family], 1
    - [Close-up picture of a man with glasses from the Thomas family], 2
    - August 18 1943 [From the Thomas family, man with glasses and woman standing outside of a house], 3
    - Verso: August 18, 1943, 3-verso
    - [Close-up of a young lady from the Thomas family], 4
    - [Pherbia Thomas and dog], 5
    - [Pherbia Thomas and dog], 6
    - [From the Thomas family, a woman standing with a fashionable umbrella], 7
    - [From the Thomas family, woman sitting in between two men], 8
    - [From the Thomas family, woman standing, holding a purse], 9
    - [From the Thomas family, two women standing and holdng flowers], 10
    - [From the Thomas family, man with arms around a woman and a young girl], 11
    - June '37 [From the Thomas family, man sitting in chair at a desk], 12
    - [From the Thomas family, man standing with dog], 13
    - [From the Thomas family, man standing with dog], 14
    - [From the Thomas family, toddler wearing a dress, standing in yard], 15
    - [From the Thoams family, portrait of a baby], 16
    - [From the Thomas family, portrait of young boy], 17
    - December 1946 [From the Thomas family, young boy with baby by the Christmas tree], 18
    - Verso: December 1946, 18-verso
    - [From the Thomas family, drawn portrait of two young girls, sitting], 19
    - [From the Thomas family, drawn portrait of two young girls, sitting], 20
    - [From the Thomas family, portrait of a young boy], 21
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family, circa 1940s; 2 (Box 1518)
    - [From the Thomas family, young girl sitting between two men (one is Lowell Thomas?) on yard in front of house. Lowell Thomas standing in front of house], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of house], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas outside, talking with unidentified man], 3
    - [Three women, unidentified man and Lowell Thomas gathered together and talking], 4
    - [Three women, unidentified man and Lowell Thomas gathered together and talking], 5
    - [Group of individuals posing for a picture on porch of house, Lowell Thomas sitting in front], 6
    - [Group of individuals posing for a picture on porch of house, Lowell Thomas sitting in front], 7
    - [Group of individuals posing for a picture on porch of house, Lowell Thomas sitting in front], 8
    - [Group of individuals posing for a picture on porch of house], 9
    - [From the Thomas family, group of people on porch, posing for a picture], 10
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family, undated; 3 (Box 1518)
    - Philip and Daddy - 2 weeks old, 1
    - Verso: Philip and Daddy - 2 weeks old, 1-verso
    - 2 weeks old, 2
    - Verso: 2 weeks old [Philip Wallou at 4 weeks with Grandmother and Aunt Mildred, 2-verso
    - 3 weeks - Brighton Canyon [From the Thomas family, woman holding baby], 3
    - Verso: 3 weeks - Brighton Canyon [Four weeks], 3-verso
    - 4 weeks old, 4
    - Verso: 4 weeks old [3 weeks - Brighton Canyon], 4-verso
    - 4 weeks old, 5
    - Verso: 4 weeks old [2 weeks old], 5-verso
    - Philip Wallace at 4 weeks with Grandmother and Aunt Mildred, 6
    - Verso: Philip Wallace at 4 weeks with Grandmother and Aunt Mildred, 6-verso
    - Taken in our garden the end of September - 3 generations!, 7
    - Verso: Taken in our garden the end of September - 3 generations!, 7-verso
    - [From the Thomas family, a father and a mother with their two children], 8
    - [From the Thomas family, woman wearing long coat standing], 9
    - [Man in military attire, walking a dog], 10
    - [From the Thomas family, portrait of a woman], 11
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family reunion, circa 1960s; 4 (Box 1518)
    - Thomas family reunion, 1
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family [Lowell, Frances and Lowell, Jr.], circa 1925 - 1940s; 5 (Box 1518)
    - J. L. Dickson, Room 650, Savarine Hotel, Jefferson Ave., Detroit, 1
    - Verso: J. L. Dickson, Room 650, Savarine Hotel, Jefferson Ave., Detroit, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, Sr. with Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas, Sr. with Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas, Sr. with Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 4
    - Lake Placid - 1932? [LT on skiis with Frances Ryan Thomas and LT, Jr.], 5
    - Verso: Lake Placid - 1932?, 5-verso
    - Mr. + Mrs. Thomas with son Lowell Jr., when the latter was 8 yrs. old, 6
    - Verso: Mr. + Mrs. Thomas with son Lowell Jr., when the latter was 8 yrs. old, 6-verso
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 7
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 8
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 9
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 10
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 11
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 12
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 13
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 14
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 15
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Thomas, Lowell, Jr., 15-verso
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 16
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 17
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 18
    - Portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr., 19
    - [Lowell Thomas, Sr., Lowell Thomas, Jr., Frances Ryan Thomas, and others on boat], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas, Sr., Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Frances Ryan Thomas by palm tree], 21
    - [L.T., Sr., L.T., Jr. and Frances Ryan Thomas together on front porch], 22
    - [L.T., Sr., L.T., Jr., and Frances Ryan Thomas together on front porch], 23
    - [L.T., Sr., L.T., Jr., and Frances Ryan Thomas together on front porch], 24
    - [L.T., Sr., and L.T., Jr., and Frances Ryan Thomas together by airplane], 25
    - [L.T., Sr. and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting, L.T., Jr. standing behind them], 26
    - [L.T., Sr. and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting, L.T., Jr. standing behind them], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas standing together], 28
    - Note: Mr. and Mrs. T. and LT, Jr.; '31 or '32, 29
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family [Lowell, Frances and Lowell, Jr.], 1968 October 18; 6 (Box 1518)
    - Note: November 8, 1968. Dear Mrs. Nicks: If you should want to use any of these for promotion or order more prints, the person to call is Shirley Baig, head of the photographic studio. Sincerely, Marylin Bender [The New York Times], 1
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 2
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 2-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 3
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 3-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 4
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 4-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 5
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 5-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 6
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 6-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 7
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 7-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 8
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 8-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 9
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 9-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 10
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 10-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 11
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and his home, at Pawling, N.Y.; 10/18/68, 11-verso
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family and friends, undated; 7 (Box 1518)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. pose at left in group photo, circa 1930], 1
    - [From the Thomas family, Lowell Thomas sitting with a group of people for a picture], 2
    - [Large group of men together for a picture], 3
    - [Group of men together for a picture], 4
    - [People lined up on horses], 5
    - Everett Marshall, 6
    - Verso: Everett Marshall, 6-verso
    - September 1902; Gertrude Viola Lamb will be 12 Dec 10, 1902, 7
    - Verso: September 1902; Gertrude Viola Lamb will be 12 Dec 10, 1902, 7-verso
    - Caption: Gertrude, 8
    - Caption: To the World's Greatest Traveloguer with best wishes, Edward J. Veasey, Jr., 9
    - Mrs. D. Thomas, 10
    - Note: Mrs. D. Thomas, 11
    - Caption: 1921, 12
    - Caption: 1921, 13
    - [Baby portrait], 14
    - [Baby], 15
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, portrait of a man], 16
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, man kneeling on one knee], 17
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, man holding baby], 18
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, two men standing together], 19
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, three women and a man standing in front of a house], 20
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, man kneeling next to little girl], 21
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, little boy lying on stomach, resting his hand on his cheek], 22
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, portrait of man], 23
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, man standing in front of forest], 24
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, portrait of a young girl], 25
    - [From Thomas' family and friends, portrait of man with mustache, cat on lap], 26
    - [Four people wrestling a pig], 27
    - Convent - Sacred Heart - St. Joseph - Mo., 28
    - [Portrait of a woman from the Thomas family], 29
    - [Young Lowell Thomas standing with another man on street with bowler hat], 30
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family - automobile race, 1914; 8 (Box 1518)
    - L.T. [Jr.(?)], 1
    - Verso: L.T., 1-verso
    - Ralph de Palma and John de [?] before race, Sat. Aug. 22 - '14, 2
    - Verso: Ralph de Palma and John de [?] before race, Sat. Aug. 22 - '14, 2-verso
    - Caption: Sat. Aug. 22 - '14, 3
    - Caption: 8 a.m., 7-22-'14, 4
    - [L.T., Jr. (?) in race car], 5
    - [Automobile race: race car], 6
    - [Automobile race: race car making a pit stop], 7
    - [At automobile race, four men climbing over wall], 8
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Thomas family - sledding, circa 1930; 9 (Box 1518)
    - The driver and brakeman are the Olympic bob - winners. Hubert and Curtis Stevens. Gee, this was a thrill! L.T. and Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 1
    - Verso: The driver and brakeman are the Olympic bob - winners. Hubert and Curtis Stevens. Gee, this was a thrill! L.T. and Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 1-verso
    - Postcard [The driver and brakeman are the Olympic bob - winners. Hubert and Curtis Stevens. Gee, this was a thrill! L.T. and Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Frances Ryan Thomas], 3
    - Sonny, Frances, Pherbia and L.T. sledding, 4
    - Verso: Sonny, Frances, Pherbia and L.T. sledding, 4-verso
    - Note: News Commentator Takes Helm on Olympic Bob Run. Lake Placid, N.Y. - Lowell Thomas popular radio broadcaster is shown steering his coaster to the Olympic bob run for a thriller with his wife, son and sister Miss Pherbia Thomas. 1/4/34, 5
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr., circa 1923 - 1930s; 10 (Box 1518)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas holding a baby], 1
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr. ?)], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr. ?)], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr. ?)], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 5
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 6
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 8
    - [(L.T., Jr.?)], 9
    - [(L.T.,Jr.?)], 10
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with two small children (L.T., Jr.?)], 11
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with two small children (L.T., Jr.?)], 12
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with two small children (L.T., Jr.?)], 13
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with two small children (L.T., Jr.?)], 14
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 15
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 16
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 17
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 18
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 19
    - [hand-colored photograph] [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 20
    - Lowell Jr. 2 yrs. [With Frances Ryan Thomas], 21
    - Verso: Lowell Jr. 2 yrs., 21-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with small child (L.T., Jr.?)], 22
    - Lowell Jr. 2 yrs. [With Frances Ryan Thomas], 23
    - Verso: Lowell Jr. 2 yrs., 23-verso
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas (?)], 24
    - [Three individuals (woman, man, and little boy) on a sled with a dog by their side], 25
    - [Woman with child (Frances Ryan Thomas ? and L.T., Jr.?)], 26
    - [Two children (Anne? and L.T., Jr.?) with skiis and dog at left], 27
    - [Boy (L.T., Jr.?) with dog in snow], 28
    - [Man and woman in snow with dog], 29
    - [Man (Lowell Thomas?) with dog in snow], 30
    - [Boy and woman (L.T., Jr.? And Frances Ryan Thomas?) on horses], 31
    - [Boy and woman (L.T., Jr.? And Frances Ryan Thomas?) on horses], 32
    - [Boy and woman (L.T., Jr.? And Frances Ryan Thomas?) on horses], 33
    - [Boy and woman (L.T., Jr.? And Frances Ryan Thomas?) on horses], 34
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and small boy (L.T., Jr.?)], 35
    - [Woman and man (L.T., Jr.?) in a field], 36
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and baby], 37
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. (in uniform), circa 1940s; 11 (Box 1518)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr. and dog], 1
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr. and dog], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr.], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thoams with L.T., Jr. in uniform], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr. in uniform], 5
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr. in uniform], 6
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr. in uniform], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr. in uniform], 8
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr. in uniform], 9
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing between L.T., Jr. and another man in uniform], 10
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr. and another man in uniform], 11
    - [(Colored photograph) Frances Ryan Thomas with L.T., Jr. and another woman], 12
  - The Thomas and Ryan families: Harry G. Thomas, 1883 - circa 1890; 12 (Box 1518)
    - Presented to Ira by Aunt Mattie Apr. 23/22 Dad and Uncle Harry. Keep this for us, 1
    - Verso: Presented to Ira by Aunt Mattie Apr. 23/22 Dad and Uncle Harry. Keep this for us, 1-verso
    - Hollansburg class 1883; From left to right - Ella D[?]; Glady [sic] Williams; Cora Ireland; Lib Moore; Will McDonald; Harry Thomas; Sam Williams; Teacher John Henspencer, 2
    - Verso: Hollansburg class 1883; From left to right - Ella D[?]; Glady [sic] Williams; Cora Ireland; Lib Moore; Will McDonald; Harry Thomas; Sam Williams; Teacher John Henspencer, 2-verso
    - [Four boys sitting in front, four girls standing in back], 3